{
    "subject": "Allan_Steiger",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Janelle_Timmins",
    "human_readable": "Allan Steiger is married to Janelle Timmins.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9873578548431396,
            "question": "Is there a marriage between Allan Steiger and Janelle Timmins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9225245714187622,
            "question": "To whom is Allan Steiger married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9190042018890381,
            "question": "Is Allan Steiger married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9138587117195129,
            "question": "Who is Allan Steiger married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9136235117912292,
            "question": "Name the person married to Janelle Timmins."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9121186137199402,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Allan Steiger and Janelle Timmins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.882011890411377,
            "question": "Who is married to Janelle Timmins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8806440830230713,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the relationship between Allan Steiger and Janelle Timmins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8722121715545654,
            "question": "Who is Janelle Timmins married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6727349162101746,
            "question": "What is the name of Janelle Timmins' spouse?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Allan Steiger is married to Janelle Timmins.",
            "html": "yago_25691_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Janelle Timmins married to?",
            "html": "yago_25691_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you tell me about the relationship between Allan Steiger and Janelle Timmins?",
            "html": "yago_25691_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is married to Janelle Timmins?",
            "html": "yago_25691_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25691_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25691_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25691_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25691_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25691_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25691_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25691_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25691_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25691_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25691_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support this triple by mentioning that Janelle Timmins (n\u00e9e Rebecchi) was played by Nell Feeney, and also by providing a biography of Janelle Timmins, which includes her marital status with Allan Steiger. Additionally, the document about Allan Steiger mentions his marriage to Janelle Timmins in 2007."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Allan Steiger and Janelle Timmins are married. Therefore, the triple \"Allan Steiger is married to Janelle Timmins\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}